# Nahla Galal

### Front-end developer

Front-end developer with 2 years experience, writing well-designed, maintainable and readable code, transforming design proposals into vabriant code. Capable of continous learning new features and tools. Helpful, flexible person and like to work in teamwork.

nahlaglal@gmail.com 🔀

+20-109-742-9922

Cairo, Egypt

https://www.linkedin.com/in/nahla-galal/

https://github.com/NahlaGalal



### **Education**

#### **Faculty of Engineering**

Mansoura university

07/2015 - 08/2020

3.64

#### ITI summer training [3]

Information Technology Institute (ITI) Mansoura

08/2018 - 09/2018

### **Work Experience**

#### OnAirCommerce WLL (07/2021 - present)

Part-time remote job

- · Convert UI designs into HTML, CSS
- Using VueJs as a separate library in some pages in laravel projects
- · Working on improving SEO and performance for applications
- · Use service worker to cache the static files

#### Freelancer (03/2021 - present)

- · Create react and react native projects.
- Worked with multiple CSS frameworks (TailwindCss, Chakra UI, Material UI, Bootstrap and antd).
- Worked on increasing applications performance and reduce rerendering components.

## **Skills**

HTML

CSS

Javascript

JQuery

SASS

reactJs T

Typescript

Redux

Git

React native

Figma

NextJs

TailwindCSS

## **Volunteer Experience**

CAT Reloaded Team (09/2018 - 08/2020)

Mentor Front-end circle

CAT Reloaded Team (09/2018 - 08/2020)

Logistics leader

ICPC Mansoura Community (04/2017 - 05/2020)

Logistics member

## **Personal Projects**

Alhamayel (07/2021 - 04/2022) [3]

Quran Tutors (12/2021 - 03/2022)

Dejavu (10/2021 - 02/2022) [3]

Code Quizzey (10/2020 - 11/2020)

Curey (11/2019 - 05/2020) [3]

My graduation project

Git clone OLX (03/2019 - 04/2019)